너는 일어서야 해
Wake up!
더 치명적인 전쟁에서
In a deadlier war
두 발로 굳건히 서서 적의 Hook에 저항하세요!
Hold on with your feet Hook!
블랙맘바
Black Mamba
당신을 두려워하지 않습니다 훗!
I am not afraid of you Hoot!
당신을 부수다
I’ll break you
우리는 변했다
It has changed
광야를 건너 돌아올 때
when we entered KWANGYA
한 번 뒤틀리고 변형된
Distorted æ
좀 더 나답게, 하나가 되듯이
more like me, like one
미친 존재의 구체화
A crazy presence that shows
또 남은 불
The ember that was left behind
큰 악으로 확장
grew into a great evil
무력하고 고립되었을 때
When I helplessly isolate you
재회하자 다시 함께하자
Reunite we’re together again
우후
Whoo Whoo
레이드 비트 잇 야
Attack Beat it Yah
당신은 혼자가 아닙니다
You’re not alone
한때 눈부셨던 희생
Shined sacrifice
기억이 회복되면
If you found the memory
좀 보게 해줄 수 있나요? 나타날 수 있나요?
Can you show us? Can you show up?
바로 지금
Right now, right here
나랑 같이 가요 (엎드려)
Follow me (Bow down)
기다려 봐 (나의 스킬)
Watch me (My skill)
와우라고 말해봐
You will get surprised (Say wow)
우리가 온다
We coming
큰 소리로
Scream (Get loud)
내 소리
Listen (My sound)
전화(업그레이드)
Call it (Upgrade)
우리가 온다
We coming
혼돈 속에 피어나는
Blooming in chaos
(우리 여자들)
(We Them Girls)
두려움에 맞서는 용기
And confronting fear, That courage
(아 그래)
(Ah Yeah)
우리가 언제 함께 있어도 상관없어
Whenever we are together
우리는 여자야 우리는 여자야
We Them Girls We Them Girls
우리는 여자야
We Them Girls
메타 유니버스는 공존하고 싶다
Meta universe exists
지금 평행세계
now Parallel world
모든 존재에는 의미가 있다
All beings have meaning
내 마음의 일부
Part of my heart
우리는 공감할 수 있는 언어를 사용합니다.
We use sympathetic words
서로 따뜻하게
and share the body temperatures
결국 추구하는 것만
In the end, we only pursue
선의의 가치
the value of goodwill
드디어 강해졌어
I finally became stronger
조작되거나 프레임화되지 않습니다.
I don’t get swindled or hurt
그리고 모든 것이 잘못 전달되었습니다.
It’s distorted
세력분열이 시작됐다
It has started again Make sides
너와 나를 고립시켜 앞을 막고
Isolate you and me so that we can’t see ahead
사악한 욕망에 뒤틀려
The algorithms that have been
폐기된 알고리즘
distorted by bad desires
존재를 무기로 삼아 파멸로 이끄는
Use existence as the weapon
삼켜 아아
and swallow with destruction Ah
그 순간 악이 시작됐다.
Evil was started at that moment
우후
Whoo Whoo
비켜가세요 플립얍
Move out flip Yah
난 혼자가 아니야
I’m not alone
보호하고 싶다
I want to protect
REKALL을 처음 만났을 때
first encountering REKALL
안아주고 느끼게 해주세요
I will hug you so that you can feel
싱크 다이브 없이
Without SYNK DIVE
나랑 같이 가요 (엎드려)
Follow me (Bow down)
기다려 봐 (나의 스킬)
Watch me (My skill)
와우라고 말해봐
You will get surprised (Say wow)
우리가 온다
We coming
큰 소리로
Scream (Get loud)
내 소리
Listen (My sound)
전화(업그레이드)
Call it (Upgrade)
우리가 온다
We coming
혼돈 속에 피어나는
Blooming in chaos
(우리 여자들)
(We Them Girls)
두려움에 맞서는 용기
And confronting fear, That courage
(아 그래)
(Ah Yeah)
우리가 언제 함께 있어도 상관없어
Whenever we are Together
우리는 여자야 우리는 여자야
We Them Girls We Them Girls
평화로운 날들에 오신 것을 환영합니다
To face a peaceful day
우리는 FLAT에 있습니다
Inside the FLAT
함께 웃고 사랑하며
We laugh and love together
친구들과 함께
With my friends
이제 nævis와 함께 더 많은 정보를 얻으세요
Now I’m more curious about
앞으로 펼쳐질 미래가 궁금해
the future together with nævis
우리는 결국 만날 것이다
Eventually we will probably meet
REAL MY WORLD의 네비스
nævis on the REAL MY WORLD
잠깐만요!
Hold up!
진짜 내 세상
REAL MY WORLD
너는 거울에 비친 나야
Your existence is brighter
그보다 더 눈부신 존재
than my reflection in the mirror
나에게 말해 줄 수 있나요?
Can you tell me?
영원히 함께 할거야
Until when, will we be together?
나랑 같이 가요 (엎드려)
Follow me (Bow down)
기다려 봐 (나의 스킬)
Watch me (My skill)
와우라고 말해봐
You will get surprised (Say wow)
우리가 온다
We coming
큰 소리로
Scream (Get loud)
내 소리
Listen (My sound)
전화(업그레이드)
Call it (Upgrade)
우리가 온다
We coming
혼돈 속에 피어나는
Blooming in chaos
(우리 여자들)
(We Them Girls)
두려움에 맞서는 용기
And confronting fear, That courage
(아 그래)
(Ah Yeah)
우리가 언제 함께 있어도 상관없어
Whenever we are together
우리는 여자야 우리는 여자야
We Them Girls We Them Girls
우리는 여자야
We Them Girls
여자애들!
Girls!